Guide to the Amos Niven Wilder and Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Amos Tappan Wilder Papers, 1983–2013; Series VIII
  - Programs saved by Tappan Wilder, 1914–2012
    - Our Town programs and photocopied reviews, 1990–1999 (Box 198, Folder 2557)
      Includes programs from productions in Washington D.C. and Costa Mesa, California.
    - Our Town Soulpepper Theatre Company photocopied reviews, programs, and posters, 1998–1999 (Box 198, Folder 2558, Box 183 (Oversize), Folder 2414)
    - Our Town Bloomsburg Theatre Ensemble photocopied reviews, postcard, and oversized poster, 1998 (Box 198, Folder 2559)
    - El Octavo Dia book, 1967 (Box 198, Folder 2561)
    - Our Town programs from productions from the American Shakespeare Theatre, Mineola Theatre, and the Plumstead Playhouse, 1968–1978 (Box 199, Folder 2562)
    - Our Town Bell Systems television production materials, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 2563)
      Includes photocopied reviews, ephemera, and photographs.
    - Our Town photocopied reviews, 1960 (Box 199, Folder 2564)
    - Our Town Albany Berkshire Ballet production program and photocopied review, 1999 (Box 199, Folder 2565)
    - Our Town opera materials, 2006–2008 (Box 199, Folder 2566)
      Includes one poster and three programs.
    - Grover's Corners materials, 1987–2006 (Box 199, Folder 2567-2568)
      Includes photographs, clippings, programs, and photocopied reviews.
    - The Matchmaker programs and oversized poster, 1958–1999 (Box 199, Folder 2569)
    - The Matchmaker programs and oversized poster, 1958–1999 (Box 122, Folder 1691)
    - One Act Plays programs, 1993–2012 (Box 199, Folder 2570)
    - Our Town programs, 2013 (Box 199, Folder 2571)
      Includes programs from productions in Moorestown, New Jersey and the Huntington Theatre Company at Boston University.
    - Our Town Peterborough Players materials, 2000–2003 (Box 199, Folder 2572)
    - Our Town program from a Hartford Stage production, 2007 (Box 199, Folder 2573)
    - Our Town Madison Repertory Theatre production clippings and programs, 2006 (Box 199, Folder 2574)
    - Our Town program from an Arden Theatre Company production, 2008 (Box 199, Folder 2575)
    - Our Town photocopied reviews from an Alley Theater production, 2009 (Box 199, Folder 2576)
    - Our Town programs, 2002–2010 (Box 199, Folder 2577-2578)
      Oversized poster is a Warehouse Theatre production poster of Our Town.
    - Our Town production materials from Writers' Theatre, 2007 (Box 200, Folder 2579)
    - Our Town La Jolla Playhouse materials, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 2580)
    - Our Town Delaware Theatre Company program, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 2581)
    - Our Town Berkeley Repertory Theatre materials, 2005 (Box 200, Folder 2582-2583)
      Includes a program, photocopied reviews, and a press packet.
    - Our Town programs and photocopied reviews, 2007 (Box 200, Folder 2584)
    - Our Town Booth Theatre production clipping, program, photographs, and negatives, 2002 (Box 200, Folder 2585)
    - Our Town photocopied reviews and American Theatre magazine clipping, 2002–2003 (Box 200, Folder 2586)
      Includes reviews from a Dallas production.
    - Our Town Westport production clippings, reviews, programs, and photocopied reviews, 2002 (Box 200, Folder 2587)
    - Our Town Masterpiece Theatre television production materials, 2003 (Box 200, Folder 2588-2589)
      Includes clippings, correspondence, and photocopied reviews.
    - Our Town Oregon Shakespeare Festival playbill, souvenir program, and ticket, 2008 (Box 200, Folder 2590)
  - Hello Dolly materials, 1960–1984
    - Division of motion picture money, 1960–1970 (Box 201, Folder 2591)
    - Motion picture correspondence, 1962–1970 (Box 201, Folder 2592-2598)
    - Motion picture agreements, 1964–1966 (Box 201, Folder 2599-2601)
    - Motion picture contracts, 1964–1969 (Box 201, Folder 2602)
    - Bus and truck tour materials, 1967–1969 (Box 201, Folder 2603)
    - Payment schedule, record royalties, and sound track royalty statements, 1966–1984 (Box 201, Folder 2604)
    - Tams-Witmark Music Library Inc. materials, 1966–1972 (Box 202, Folder 2605-2606)
    - Motion picture release materials, 1967–1971 (Box 202, Folder 2607)
    - Sound track royalties and correspondence, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 2608-2609)
    - Stage correspondence, clippings, and agreements, 1966–1972 (Box 202, Folder 2610-2613)
    - Producers' participation rights, 1964–1971 (Box 202, Folder 2614)
    - Agreements, 1964–1969 (Box 203, Folder 2615-2616)
    - Matchmaker Company materials, 1966–1969 (Box 203, Folder 2617)
  - Correspondence and business related materials, 1928–2011
    Box 204-221 and 405-408 restricted until 2029. Please consult the appropriate curator for more details.
    - Our Town materials
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2005–2006 (Box 405, Folder 5230-5231)
      - Italian production related correspondence, 2005–2007 (Box 405, Folder 5232-5233)
      - Scott Hamilton Kennedy printed email correspondence and related materials, 2002–2009 (Box 405, Folder 5234-5235)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2002–2003 (Box 405, Folder 5236-5237)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2003–2004 (Box 405, Folder 5238-5239)
      - Musical related agreement and correspondence, 1996 October (Box 405, Folder 5240)
      - Extension agreements and related materials, 1998 April (Box 405, Folder 5241-5242)
      - Samuel French short plays correspondence and related materials, 1998–2002 (Box 406, Folder 5243-5244)
      - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency Inc. Tams- Witmark Music Library and copyright search materials, 2002–2009 (Box 406, Folder 5245)
      - Theatre productions and television adaptations printed email correspondence, 2009–2010 (Box 406, Folder 5246)
      - Russell Redmond printed email correspondence and untitled script, 2009 (Box 406, Folder 5247)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth Young Vic production, 2003–2004 (Box 406, Folder 5248-5249)
      - Jo's Town materials, 2002 (Box 406, Folder 5250)
      - Irina Brook French adaptation materials, 2004 April (Box 406, Folder 5251)
      - Foreign productions printed correspondence, 2005 (Box 406, Folder 5252-5253)
      - Frank Oz correspondence regarding The Skin of Our Teeth motion picture rights, 2000–2005 (Box 406, Folder 5254)
      - High Town film adaptation correspondence, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 5255)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth musical adaptation materials, 2005–2008 (Box 407, Folder 5256-5258)
      - Barrow Street Theater production agreements, 2008 December 22 (Box 407, Folder 5259)
      - Our Town Revisited script and related materials, 2008–2009 (Box 407, Folder 5260-5261)
      - Amateur production requests, 2009–2011 (Box 407, Folder 5262-5264)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth clippings, correspondence, and fax copies, 1996–2002 (Box 407, Folder 5265-5267)
        This marks the portion of this box that is not restricted.
      - Trinity Repertory Company materials, 2006–2007 (Box 408, Folder 5268-5269)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth musical related materials, 2002–2009 (Box 408, Folder 5270-5272)
      - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency Inc. correspondence regarding Lee Hoiby music, 1996–1997 (Box 204, Folder 2618)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth related printed email correspondence, 2008–2011 (Box 204, Folder 2619-2620)
      - Play production printed email correspondence, 2007 January (Box 204, Folder 2621-2623)
        Includes correspondence about productions of The Matchmaker and One Act Plays.
      - Play production printed email correspondence, 2007–2008 (Box 204, Folder 2624-2625)
      - Play production printed email correspondence, 2009 April (Box 204, Folder 2626-2627)
      - Play production printed email correspondence, 2008 January (Box 204, Folder 2628-2630)
      - Play production printed email correspondence (Box 205, Folder 2631)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth musical progams and related materials, 2006–2007 (Box 205, Folder 2632-2633)
      - Miscellaneous play production materials, 1997–1998 (Box 205, Folder 2634-2636)
        Includes mostly photocopied materials related to One Act Plays.
      - Play production printed email correspondence, 2007 January (Box 205, Folder 2637-2639)
      - Our Town production printed email correspondence, 2009–2010 (Box 206, Folder 2640-2641)
      - Play production printed email correspondence, clippings, and ephemera, 2006 (Box 206, Folder 2642-2644)
      - Our Town production printed email correspondence and related materials, 2004–2005 (Box 206, Folder 2645-2647)
      - Our Town production printed email correspondence and related materials, 2004 (Box 207, Folder 2648-2650)
      - Our To wn production printed email correspondence and related materials, 2009–2010 (Box 207, Folder 2651-2652)
      - Play productions printed email correspondence and related materials, 2004–2005 (Box 207, Folder 2653-2654)
      - Play productions printed email correspondence and related materials, 2004 (Box 207, Folder 2655-2657)
      - Our Town clippings, printed email correspondence, and related materials, 2002–2003 (Box 207, Folder 2658-2659)
      - Our Town and Grover's Corners printed correspondence and related materials, 1999 (Box 208, Folder 2660-2661)
      - Roundabout Theatre production correspondence, clippings, and related materials, 2002 February (Box 208, Folder 2662-2663)
      - South Korean productions correspondence and related materials, 2006–2007 (Box 208, Folder 2664)
      - Play productions printed email correspondence, clippings, and related materials, 2009 (Box 208, Folder 2665-2667)
      - General contract and agreement printed corrsepondence, 2008–2010 (Box 208, Folder 2668-2669)
      - Our Town and Our Town Revisited productions printed email correspondence, 2008–2009 (Box 208, Folder 2670-2672)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2007 (Box 209, Folder 2673-2675)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2006 (Box 209, Folder 2676-2677)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2009–2010 (Box 209, Folder 2678-2680)
      - Printed email correspondence and related materials, 2008–2010 (Box 210, Folder 2681-2683)
    - Union Trust correspondence and related materials, 1976–1990 (Box 210, Folder 2684)
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. correspondence and related materials, 1998–1999 (Box 210, Folder 2685)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents Inc. Theophilus North and The Eighth Day cheques, 1996 October (Box 210, Folder 2686)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency correspondence, 1984–1995 (Box 210, Folder 2687)
    - Bills, 1996 (Box 210, Folder 2688-2690)
      Includes Amos Tappan's printed expenses and notes.
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. correspondence and related materials, 1996–1998 (Box 211, Folder 2691-2693)
    - Penelope Niven correspondence and related materials, 1996–2004 (Box 211, Folder 2694-2696)
    - F. J. O'Neil materials, 1998–1999 (Box 211, Folder 2697-2698)
    - Printed fax transmissions, 1995–1996 (Box 211, Folder 2699-2700)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents Inc. Theophilus North and The Bridge of San Luis Rey correspondence, 1987 January–1988 October (Box 211, Folder 2701)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information, 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2702)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information, 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2703-2704)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information, 2002 (Box 212, Folder 2705-2707)
      Also includes the Penguin Group and Yale University Press materials.
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information (5 folders), 2002 (Box 212, Folder 2708-2712)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency special account materials (1), 1995 (Box 213, Folder 2713-2721)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency special account materials (1), 1995 (Box 214, Folder 2722-2724)
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. correspondence and related materials, 1999 (Box 215, Folder 2725)
    - Caroline Maun correspondence and photocopied research, 2009–2011 (Box 215, Folder 2726-2728)
      Caroline Maun researched Charlotte Wilder's work.
    - Collected Short Plays correspondence and related materials, 1995–1997 (Box 215, Folder 2729-2730)
    - Ellen Wilhite administrative assistance invoices, 2005–2006 (Box 215, Folder 2731)
    - Gertrude Stein clippings and photocopied articles, 2005–2007 (Box 215, Folder 2732)
    - J.D. McClatchy correspondence and clippings, 1998–2006 (Box 215, Folder 2733)
    - F. J. O'Neil materials, 1977–1998 (Box 215, Folder 2734-2737)
    - Paula Kimper correspondence, 2005–2010 (Box 216, Folder 2738)
    - Sol Jaffe correspondence, 1975–1987 (Box 216, Folder 2739)
    - John Barnett correspondence, 1995–1997 (Box 216, Folder 2740-2741)
    - Wilder estate management correspondence, 1995 (Box 216, Folder 2742-2743)
    - Franklin, Weinrib, Rudell & Vassallo P.C. correspondence, 1998–1999 (Box 216, Folder 2744)
    - Thornton Wilder website printed materials, 1996–1999 (Box 216, Folder 2745-2747)
    - Yale University Press correspondence and related materials, 1995–1996 (Box 216, Folder 2748)
    - Yale University Press correspondence and related materials, 1995–1996 (Box 217, Folder 2749-2750)
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. correspondence and related materials, 1994–1996 (Box 217, Folder 2751-2753)
    - F. J. O'Neil materials, 1996–1997 (Box 217, Folder 2754-2756)
    - Polish rights, 1961–2004 (Box 218, Folder 2757)
    - Dianna Pickens correspondence, 2008–2009 (Box 218, Folder 2758)
    - Photocopied The Bridge of San Luis Rey articles in Spanish, undated (Box 218, Folder 2759)
    - Martin Hilsky, Hungarian translator, photocopied correspondence and related materials, 1998 (Box 218, Folder 2760)
    - Italian translations and productions correspondence and related materials, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 2761)
    - Paolo Poli's The Bridge of San Luis Rey stage production correspon dence and photocopied articles, 2005 (Box 218, Folder 2762-2764)
    - Julie Vatain correspondence, 2005–2009 (Box 218, Folder 2765)
    - Thierry Greyboeuf correspondence, 1996–2005 (Box 218, Folder 2766)
    - Irina Brook clippings and ephemera, 2004–2010 (Box 218, Folder 2767-2768)
    - Societe des Auteurs I materials, 1946–2010 (Box 218, Folder 2769)
      Some materials include annotations in Thornton Wilder's hand.
    - Societe des Auteurs II materials, 2005–2006 (Box 218, Folder 2770)
    - Our Town production in China materials, 1986–2004 (Box 218, Folder 2771)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information, 2005 (Box 219, Folder 2772-2774)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summary of financial information, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 2775-2778)
    - Penguin Group and Brandt & Hochman Literary Agents, Inc. summaries of financial information and related materials, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 2779)
    - Brandt & Hochman Literary Agents, Inc. summaries of financial information, 2004 (Box 219, Folder 2780)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summaries of financial information, 2001 (Box 220, Folder 2781-2784)
    - Brandt & Hochman Literary Agents, Inc. summaries of financial information, 2001 (Box 220, Folder 2785)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents, Inc, Penguin Group, Yale University Press and other royalty statements, 1999 (Box 220, Folder 2786-2787)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summaries of financial information, 1999 (Box 220, Folder 2788-2791)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency summaries of financial information, 1999 (Box 221, Folder 2792)
    - Robert A. Freedman Dramatic Agency faxes and related materials, 2000 (Box 221, Folder 2793-2794)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth productions correspondence, payment information, and related materials, 1996–2000 (Box 221, Folder 2795-2797)
    - Hello Dolly and The Matchmaker productions correspondence and related materials, 2002–2003 (Box 221, Folder 2798-2799)
    - Play correspondence and related materials, 1999–2001 (Box 221, Folder 2800-2801)
  - Contracts
    - Cogan agreement issues, 2009 (Box 222, Folder 2802)
    - Playscripts Inc. correspondence, 2009 August 2 (Box 222, Folder 2803)
    - Contracts holding file, 2008–2012 (Box 222, Folder 2804)
      Includes agreements and correspondence.
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey, The Matchmaker, and the Thornton Wilder biography agreements, 2012 (Box 222, Folder 2805)
    - Our Town, The Bridge of San Luis Rey, the biography and other works agreements, 2011 (Box 222, Folder 2806-2808)
    - Play production agreements and The Secret Historian related correspondence, 2010 (Box 222, Folder 2809-2810)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth and other works agreements, 2009 (Box 222, Folder 2811)
    - Our Town and other works agreements, 2008 (Box 222, Folder 2812-2813)
    - Play license agreements and related materials, 2007 (Box 222, Folder 2814)
    - Book and play agreements, 2006 (Box 222, Folder 2815)
    - Our Town and The Bridge of San Luis Rey agreements, 2005 (Box 222, Folder 2816)
    - License agreements for multiple works, 2004 (Box 222, Folder 2817)
    - Our Town, The Bridge of San Luis Rey, and The Paris Review agreements, 2003 (Box 222, Folder 2818)
    - Harper Collins Publishers amendments and agreements, 2002 (Box 222, Folder 2819)
    - Poetry correspondence, 2001 (Box 222, Folder 2820)
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. agreements, 2000 (Box 222, Folder 2821)
    - Barbara Hogenson Agency Inc. correspondence and related materials, 1999 (Box 222, Folder 2822)
    - Photocopied Edward Burns correspondence, 1998 (Box 222, Folder 2823)
    - Photocopied Yale Review agreement, 1997 (Box 222, Folder 2824)
    - Photocopied Harper Collins Publishers correspondence, 1996 (Box 222, Folder 2825)
    - Programs and reviews in French, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 2826)
    - Books and research, 1988–2010 (Box 223, Folder 2827)
    - Thornton Niven Wilder Award photocopied correspondence and ephemera, circa 2007 (Box 223, Folder 2828)
      Materials refer to the Thornton Niven Wilder Award at the Translation Center at Columbia University.
    - Japanese productions typescript and photocopied correspondence, 1949; undated (Box 223, Folder 2829)
    - Photocopied articles in Ruissian, 1997 (Box 223, Folder 2830)
    - Tatiana Kabanova correspondence and related materials, 1996–2006 (Box 223, Folder 2831)
    - Slavic University publications materials, 1997–1998 (Box 223, Folder 2832)
    - Agents correspondence, 1994–2004 (Box 223, Folder 2833)
    - French photocopied articles and correspondence, 2001–2004 (Box 223, Folder 2834)
    - Photocopied and printed articles in English and French, 2003; undated
    - U.S.I. A photocopied articles, undated (Box 223, Folder 2835)
    - Photocopied and typescript Thornton Wilder correspondence, 2006 (Box 223, Folder 2836)
    - Photocopied Thornton Wilder articles and correspondence, undated (Box 223, Folder 2837)
    - The Merchant of Yonkers, The Matchmaker, and Hello Dolly contracts
      - The Merchant of Yonkers photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2838)
      - The Matchmaker photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2839, Folder 2839a-2839b)
      - Hello Dolly photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2840)
  - Classic one act plays photocopied contracts
    - Classic one act plays photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2841)
    - The Long Christmas Dinner photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2842)
    - Queens of France photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2843)
    - Pullman Car Hiwatha photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2844)
    - Love and How to Cure It photocopied contracts, undated (Box 223, Folder 2845)
    - Such Things Only Happen in Books photocopied contracts, undated (Box 224, Folder 2846)
    - The Happy Journey to Trenton and Camden, photocopied contracts, undated (Box 224, Folder 2846a)
  - Photocopied agreements and correspondence
    - The Eighth Day photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 224, Folder 2847)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 224, Folder 2848-2850)
    - The Ides of March photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2851-2852)
    - Short plays photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2853)
      Includes agreements for The Alcestiad, The Drunken Sisters, and the Seven Deadly Sins plays.
    - Miscellaneous photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2854)
    - American Characteristics translations photocopied correspondence and The Wreck on the Five Twenty Five agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2855)
    - The Cabala photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2856)
    - The Alcestiad photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2857)
    - Theophilus North photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2858)
    - Anthologies photocopied articles, undated (Box 224, Folder 2859)
    - Heaven's My Destination photocopied agreements, undated (Box 224, Folder 2860)
    - Heaven's My Destination photocopied agreements, undated (Box 225, Folder 2861)
    - The Woman of Andros photocopied agreements, undated (Box 225, Folder 2862)
    - The Ages of Man photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 225, Folder 2863-2864)
    - Three Minute Plays photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 225, Folder 2865)
    - The Angel that Troubled the Waters photocopied agreements, undated (Box 225, Folder 2866)
    - Agency trustee power of attorney photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 225, Folder 2867-2868)
    - Anthologies photocopied agreements and correspondence, undated (Box 225, Folder 2869)
    - Thornton Wilder reader in German photocopied correspondence, undated (Box 225, Folder 2870)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents, Inc. agreements and correspondence, 1992–1995 (Box 225, Folder 2871)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents, Inc. agreements and correspondence, 1982–1989 (Box 225, Folder 2872)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents, Inc. agreements and correspondence, 1974–1978 (Box 225, Folder 2873)
    - Spanish language translation agreements for The Skin of Our Teeth, The Matchmaker, Our Town, The Bridge of San Luis Rey, and The Woman of Andros, circa 1960 (Box 225, Folder 2874)
    - Brandt & Brandt Literary Agents, Inc. agreements and other agreements, 1928–1986 (Box 225, Folder 2875-2876)
    - Permissions materials and The Paris Review correspondence, 2003–2011 (Box 225, Folder 2877)
    - Translator resumes, circa 2009 (Box 225, Folder 2878)
  - Correspondence and personal papers
    - Gene Tunney correspondence and photocopied articles, 2008–2010 (Box 226, Folder 2879)
    - Samuel Ziskind and Richard Goldstone correspondence and related materials, 1996–2011 (Box 226, Folder 2880-2881)
    - Donald C. Gallup correspondence and obituary clipping, 1995–2000 (Box 226, Folder 2882)
    - Edward Burns correspondence and research files, 1998–2000 (Box 226, Folder 2883-2885)
      Includes typescript copies of Thornton Wilder's correspondence with Adaline Glasheen.
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey radio broadcast related correspondence, 1928–2007 (Box 226, Folder 2886-2887)
    - French language productions photocopied clippings and correspondence, circa 1990 (Box 226, Folder 2888)
    - Editions Gallimard photocopied correspondence and royalties, 2004–2008 (Box 226, Folder 2889-2890)
    - Caroline Maun correspondence and photocopied articles, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 2891)
    - Donald C. Gallup correspondence, photocopied, and printed articles, 1985–2000 (Box 226, Folder 2892)
    - The Company We Kept bound book of reminiscenes, 1998 (Box 226, Folder 2893)